HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride - Rev. James Lawson -- 5/17/2003; Houston Kick-Off Event - 6/14/2003, 4 (Box 11)
- SAT #2, 5 (Box 11)
- SAT #3, 6 (Box 11)
- SAT #1, 7 (Box 11)
- FRI #5, 8 (Box 11)
- FRI #1, 9 (Box 11)
- FRI#2, 10 (Box 11)
- FRI #3, 11 (Box 11)
- FRI #4, 12 (Box 11)
- THR #1, 13 (Box 11)
- THR #2, 14 (Box 11)
- THR #3, 15 (Box 11)
- THR #4, 16 (Box 11)
- We Serve the Public, 17 (Box 11)
  A behind the scenes view of Union members and the International Office
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention Highlights -- 10/18/1991, 18 (Box 11)
- HERE Local 274 - Flex Plan -- 10/31/1995, 19 (Box 11)
- Shackled Children, 20 (Box 11)
- Culinary Employees Union, Local 777 - 30 Second Commercial "Message from Las Vegas", 21 (Box 11)
- At your service - date: 11/9/1995; I was fired & the union got me my TCB back, 22 (Box 11)
- One Day Longer: the Story of the Frontier Strike, 1 (Box 12)
- One Day Longer: the Story of the Frontier Strike, 2 (Box 12)
- Hotel & Spa - Workers Unite, 3 (Box 12)
- One Day Longer - 2000 version, 4 (Box 12)
- One Day Longer: the story of the Frontier Strike, 5 (Box 12)
- Local Union Videos "Educate" convention 1996, 6 (Box 12)
- Support HERE Local 75 Strikers, 7 (Box 12)
- Culinary/Frontier Picket Line Incident - 68 cuts from 4/28-5/9/1993, 8 (Box 12)
- Victory Announcement of the Frontier Strike Ending in Las Vegas, 9 (Box 12)
- Rise up! the Hilton Victory, 10 (Box 12)
- Victory is ours! The Frontier Strikers Win in Las Vegas, 11 (Box 12)
- Above the Law, 12 (Box 12)
- Local Union Video - "Educate" - Convention 1996, 13 (Box 12)
- Turning Point - Justice at the Horseshoe -- Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 14 (Box 12)
- Culinary Workers Union, Local 226 - Membership Mtg. 10/6/1994, 15 (Box 12)
- Windows, 16 (Box 12)
- Culinary Workers Union, Local 226 - Membership Mtg. 10/6/1994, 17 (Box 12)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees Health Fund - For Your Benefit, 18 (Box 12)
- In Their Own Hands: the Las Vegas Housekeepers Story, 19 (Box 12)
- In their Own Hands: the Las Vegas Housekeepers Story, 20 (Box 12)
- In Their Own Hands: The Las Vegas Housekeepers Story, 21 (Box 12)
- Hungry for Justice - HERE Local 1, 22 (Box 12)
- HERE: Frontier Strike Over Las Vagas -- 1/31/1998, 23 (Box 12)
- The DC Labor Peace Law for New Hotel Development - 5/29/2003, 24 (Box 12)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention - Highlights, 25 (Box 12)
- Local 25 -: What I need Rally" -- 2/23/1986, 26 (Box 12)
- Fighting for our union, 27 (Box 12)
- Fighting for our union, 28 (Box 12)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 1 (Box 13)
- Tuesday - July 9 -- HERE Convention, 2 (Box 13)
- Tuesday - July 9 -- HERE Convention, 3 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 4 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 5 (Box 13)
- Thursday - July 11, 1991 - Pre-Show shot of Juliano -- HERE Convention, 6 (Box 13)
- Thursday - July 11 -- HERE Convention, 7 (Box 13)
- Thursday - July 11 -- HERE Convention, 8 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 9 (Box 13)
- Day 3, Tape 8 -- HERE Convention, 10 (Box 13)
- Thursday - July 11 -- HERE Convention, 11 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 12 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 13 (Box 13)
- Wednesday - July 10 -- HERE Convention, 14 (Box 13)
- Tuesday - July 9 -- HERE Convention, 15 (Box 13)
- Windows, 1 (Box 14)
- At your service: Its labor back in DC -- 2/13/1997, 2 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #112, 3 (Box 14)
- Tenure Commission - Show #117, 4 (Box 14)
- At Your Service - Show #59 - IBEW, 5 (Box 14)
- At Your Service - #67, 6 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #54 - James Baxter - Candidate at large - 10/24/1996, 7 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #112, 8 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #55 -- Paul Regan Legal Services -- 10/24/1996, 9 (Box 14)
- At Your Service -- Irish Youth Exchange Program, 10 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #230 - Political Roundtable -- 9/21/2000, 11 (Box 14)
- At Your Service -- 1/27/2000, 12 (Box 14)
- We're the Ones, 13 (Box 14)
- At Your Service Show #108 -- Political Roundtable - 2/5/1998, 14 (Box 14)
- Show #118 - D.C. Correction Officers, 15 (Box 14)
- DC Schools Where is the money - Show #116, 16 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #56 -- Sandy Allen - Ward 8, 17 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #68 -- Who's Answering the phone, 18 (Box 14)
- Show #119 - Women's Law Project, 19 (Box 14)
- At Your Service - #65 -- Labor's Impact on the 1996 Elections -- 1/16/1997, 20 (Box 14)
- At Your Service -- Show #111 -- Ending Rent Control -- 2/19/1998, 21 (Box 14)
- At Your Service -- Show #110 -- Medical Malpractice Reform? -- 2/19/1998, 22 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #113, 23 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #66, 24 (Box 14)
- Tenure Commission -- Show #117, 25 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #231 -- Strike at Washington Hospital Center -- 9/28/2000, 26 (Box 14)
- At Your Service - Show #60 -- DC Shadow Reps Pt. 1, 27 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #112, 28 (Box 14)
- At Your Service #243 - Political Round Table Pt. 1 -- 2/14/2000, 29 (Box 14)
- HERE Int. Union, Executive Board Meeting -- 5/15/2000, 30 (Box 14)
- HERE Intl. Union, Executive Board Meeting -- 5/15/2000, 31 (Box 14)
  tape #1 of 5
- At Your Service #243 - Political Round Table Pt. 1 -- 2/14/2000, 32 (Box 14)
- HERE Intl. Union, Executive Board Meeting -- 5/15/2000, 33 (Box 14)
  Tape #5 of 5
- HERE, Executive Board Meeting -- 5/15/2000, 34 (Box 14)
  Tape #4 of 5
- HERE Intl. Union, Executive Board Meeting -- 5/15/2000, 35 (Box 14)
- Turning Point: Justice at the Horseshoe - Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 1 (Box 15)
- Turning Point: Justice at the Horseshoe - Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 2 (Box 15)
- Turning Point: Justice at the Horseshoe - Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 3 (Box 15)
- Windows, 4 (Box 15)
- Windows, 5 (Box 15)
- Hotel, Motel & Restaurant Employees & Bartender's Union - Local 471-AFL-CIO, 6 (Box 15)
- Hotel, Motel & Restaurant Employees & Bartender's Union - Local 471-AFL-CIO, 7 (Box 15)
- Building Bridges - v. 1, 1997; 8 (Box 15)
- Sky, 9 (Box 15)
- Sky Chefs Convention, 10 (Box 15)
- Sky Chefs Convention, 11 (Box 15)
- Out of the Shadows: A story from the heart of working America, 12 (Box 15)
- Local 21: Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant and Tavern Employees Union, 1999; 13 (Box 15)
- At Your Service - "Irish Youth Exchange Program" -- 7/7/1998, 14 (Box 15)
- Testimony of Culinary Workers Union - Local 226 -- National Gambling Impact Study Commission, Las Vegas, November 10-11, 1998, 15 (Box 15)
- The 5th Annual Distinguished Labor Leader Lecture - "Hospitality Begins with a Quality Union Contract: the Union's Role in Reviving the Industry", 16 (Box 15)
- Washington March -- News Cuts -- 8/31/1994 -- Solidarity Day, 17 (Box 15)
- HERE Security for Life - 6/12/1991, 18 (Box 15)
- Broken Promise -- 4/10/1991, 19 (Box 15)
- Broken Promises -- 4/10/1991, 20 (Box 15)
- Capitol Hill Hearing -- HERE -- 7/21/1999, 21 (Box 15)
  tapes 1-4
- Capitol Hill Hearing -- HERE -- 7/21/1999, 22 (Box 15)
- HERE Politics: Behind the Scenes, 23 (Box 15)
- Broken Promise -- 4/10/1991, 24 (Box 15)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union -- Las Vegas -- 5/31/1984, 25 (Box 15)
- 3 Shots from SP "Vegas" -- 5/21/1984, 26 (Box 15)
- At Your Service #68 -- Who's Answering the Phone, 1 (Box 16)
- Celebrating Our Victories - HERE Local 75, 2 (Box 16)
- Chicago Hotel Contract 2002 -- Fox News with Walter Jacobson, 3 (Box 16)
  Channel 32- February 21, 2002
- Chicago Hotel Contract 2002 -- Fox News with Walter Jacobson, 4 (Box 16)
  Channel 32 - February 21, 2002
- Yale Strike Video, 5 (Box 16)
- Local 21 -- Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant and Tavern Employees Union, 1999; 6 (Box 16)
- At Your Service #112, 7 (Box 16)
- Unlabeled, 8 (Box 16)
  Audio tape pulled from 6199/005 P, Box 26 and added here
- Hail to the Cook, 9 (Box 16)
- Americans at Work, 10 (Box 16)
- We Serve the Public, 11 (Box 16)
- HERE Convention - Chicago, Illinois, 12 (Box 16)
- AD Ban Presentation, 13 (Box 16)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union -- Lost Vegas -- 5/31/1984, 14 (Box 16)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention - Highlights, 15 (Box 16)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention - Highlights, 16 (Box 16)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention - Highlights, 17 (Box 16)
- We Serve the Public, 18 (Box 16)
- Americans at Work, 19 (Box 16)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention - Highlights, 20 (Box 16)
- Culinary Workers Local 226 - Prime Time Live -- 10/2/1996, 21 (Box 16)
- We're the Ones, 22 (Box 16)
- What Really Happened in Florida, 23 (Box 16)
- Hail to the Cook, 24 (Box 16)
- HERE International Union: Organizing to Win, 25 (Box 16)
  Labor Productions
- HERE International Union: Organizing to Win, 26 (Box 16)
- Excerpts From Wayne Newton - HERE Las Vegas Strike Concert -- 6/3/1985, 27 (Box 16)
- The Whiteville Choir -- UNITE! Local 1077, 1 (Box 17)
- Looking Back Moving Forward, 1 (Box 18)
- Looking Back Moving Forward, 1 (Box 19)